

# Kristiyan Omayski

Youth Football Coach Age groups U5 - U13



#### **About Me**

**UEFA C licensed** football coach with a strong focus on early-age player development U5-U7. Experienced in coaching U5-U12 groups, using interactive methods like PowerPoint, Google Forms, and Excel to enhance engagement and structure. Skilled in planning methology Kimet, Soccer Sketch and video analysis using Veo camera. Proven leadership through mentoring roles in youth coach intern programs. Also interested in technology and coding with Python.



# **Certificates**

- ▶ <u>UEFA "C" Certificate</u>
- National "C" Certificate
- ► Football Instructor Certificate



### Contact

- 0893447354
- k.omayski@abv.bg
- Sofia, Bulgaria
- www.kristiyan-omayski.com
- in Kristiyan Omayski



## **Experience**

• Football Coach

UFC "Sofia - 1992", Sofia/Bulgaria

#### 08/2021 - Present

- ▶ Working with young age groups from U5 to U13 Integrating interactive ways in the training process like
- ▶ PowerPoint presentations, quizzes with Google forms and Excel schedule templates
- Using football planning software Kimet
- Creating training plans with Soccer Sketch
- Operating with Veo camera and it's site application
- Lead role in the club's intern program for youth coaches
- Football Coach

FC "Ultrasport - Academy", Sofia/Bulgaria

#### 08/2017 - 08/2021

- ► Creating weekly and monthly schedules of training procces
- Organizing summer training camps

#### Education

Professional Qualification <u>Python Software Engineer</u>

Software University (SoftUni), Sofia/Bulgaria

10/2022 - 12/2024

- Certificates for all courses
- Bachelor's degree in Journalism

University of National and World Economics, Sofia/Bulgaria

- 09/2015 07/2019
- High School Diploma in Economics

23rd SOU "Frederic Joliot-Curie", Sofia/Bulgaria

09/2011 - 05/2015